ILGWU Association Agreements, Out-of-Business Contracts 5780/145
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Manufacturers Council of the Ladies Cloak and Suit Industry of the Province of Quebec, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Manufacturers Council of the Ladies Cloak and Suit Industry of the Province of Quebec, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- The Montreal Manufacturers Council, Women's Apparel Industry (new name ), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Amended 8/72
- The Montreal Manufacturers Council, Women's Apparel Industry (new name ), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Amended 10/72
- The Montreal Manufacturers Council, Women's Apparel Industry (new name ), 1973-1976 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- The Montreal Manufacturers Council, Women's Apparel Industry (new name ), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Manufacturers Council of the Ladies Cloak and Suit Industry of the Province of Quebec, 1960-1962 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- The Montreal Manufacturers Council, Women's Apparel Industry (new name ), 1970-1973 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Manufacturers Council of the Ladies Cloak and Suit Industry of the Province of Quebec, 1948-1949 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Manufacturers Council of the Ladies Cloak and Suit Industry of the Province of Quebec, 1945-1946 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Manufacturers Council of the Ladies Cloak and Suit Industry of the Province of Quebec, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Manufacturers Council of the Ladies Cloak and Suit Industry of the Province of Quebec, 1957-1960 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Manufacturers Council of the Ladies Cloak and Suit Industry of the Province of Quebec, 1949-1951 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Manufacturers Council of the Ladies Cloak and Suit Industry of the Province of Quebec, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Manufacturers Council of the Ladies Cloak and Suit Industry of the Province of Quebec, 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Manufacturers Council of the Ladies Cloak and Suit Industry of the Province of Quebec, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Manufacturers Council of the Ladies Cloak and Suit Industry of the Province of Quebec, 1952-1955 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Manufacturers Council of the Ladies Cloak and Suit Industry of the Province of Quebec, 1955-1957 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Manufacturers Council of the Ladies Cloak and Suit Industry of the Province of Quebec, 1946-1948 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- The Montreal Manufacturers Council, Women's Apparel Industry (new name ), 1975 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- The Montreal Manufacturers Council, Women's Apparel Industry (new name ), 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- The Montreal Manufacturers Council, Women's Apparel Industry (new name ), 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- The Montreal Manufacturers Council, Women's Apparel Industry (new name ), 1980-1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- The Belt Manufacturers Association of Montreal Inc, 1977-1980 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- The Belt Manufacturers Association of Montreal Inc, 1972-1975 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- The Belt Manufacturers Association of Montreal Inc, 1969-1972 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- The Belt Manufacturers Association of Montreal Inc, 1966-1969 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Fashion Accessories Manufacturers Association (Montreal) (name changed), 1952-1955 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Pleating and Embroidery Manufacturers Association (Montreal), 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Pleating and Embroidery Manufacturers Association (Montreal), 1938-1940 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Pleating and Embroidery Manufacturers Association (Montreal), 1940-1942 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Pleating and Embroidery Manufacturers Association (Montreal), 1942-1944 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Pleating and Embroidery Manufacturers Association (Montreal), 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Fashion Accessories Manufacturers Association (Montreal) (name changed), 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Fashion Accessories Manufacturers Association (Montreal) (name changed), 1947-1949 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Fashion Accessories Manufacturers Association (Montreal) (name changed), 1973-1976 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Fashion Accessories Manufacturers Association (Montreal) (name changed), 1970-1973 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Fashion Accessories Manufacturers Association (Montreal) (name changed), 1968 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Fashion Accessories Manufacturers Association (Montreal) (name changed), 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Fashion Accessories Manufacturers Association (Montreal) (name changed), 1964-1967 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Fashion Accessories Manufacturers Association (Montreal) (name changed), 1961-1964 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Fashion Accessories Manufacturers Association (Montreal) (name changed), 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Fashion Accessories Manufacturers Association (Montreal) (name changed), 1949-1952 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Fashion Accessories Manufacturers Association (Montreal) (name changed), 1958-1961 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Fashion Accessories Manufacturers Association (Montreal) (name changed), 1984 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Fashion Accessories Manufacturers Association (Montreal) (name changed), 1987-1990 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Fashion Accessories Manufacturers Association (Montreal) (name changed), 1990-1993 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Fashion Accessories Manufacturers Association (Montreal) (name changed), 1981-1984 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Fashion Accessories Manufacturers Association (Montreal) (name changed), 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Fashion Accessories Manufacturers Association (Montreal) (name changed), 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Fashion Accessories Manufacturers Association (Montreal) (name changed), 1984-1987 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Vancouver Apparel Manufacturers' Guild, 1960-1962 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Vancouver Apparel Manufacturers' Guild, 1962-1964 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Vancouver Ladies' Garment Manufacturers Association, 1953-1957 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Vancouver Ladies' Garment Manufacturers Association, 1958-1960 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Vancouver Ladies' Garment Manufacturers Association, 1948-1952 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Vancouver Ladies' Garment Manufacturers Association, 1946-1948 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Vancouver Ladies' Garment Manufacturers Association, 1942-1944 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Vancouver Ladies' Garment Manufacturers Association, 1940-1942 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Vancouver Ladies' Garment Manufacturers Association, 1938-1940 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Vancouver Ladies' Garment Manufacturers Association, 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Vancouver Ladies' Garment Manufacturers Association, 1944-1946 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Winnipeg Ladies' Cloak and Suit Manufacturers' Association (new name), 1945-1947 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Winnipeg Ladies' Cloak and Suit Manufacturers' Association (new name), 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Winnipeg Ladies' Cloak and Suit Manufacturers' Association (new name), 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Winnipeg Ladies' Cloak and Suit Manufacturers' Association (new name), 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Winnipeg Ladies' Cloak and Suit Manufacturers' Association (new name), 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Winnipeg Ladies' Cloak and Suit Manufacturers' Association (new name), 1961-1964 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Winnipeg Ladies' Cloak and Suit Manufacturers' Association (new name), 1958-1961 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Winnipeg Ladies Garment Manufacturers Association, 1935-1937 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Winnipeg Ladies' Cloak and Suit Manufacturers' Association (new name), 1948-1952 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Winnipeg Ladies Garment Manufacturers Association, 1939-1944 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Winnipeg Ladies Garment Manufacturers Association, 1937-1939 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Winnipeg Ladies' Cloak and Suit Manufacturers' Association (new name), 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Winnipeg Ladies' Cloak and Suit Manufacturers' Association (new name), 1953-1957 (Box 7, Folder 9)